Finding Aid for the The Donald Grady Davidson Papers
Special Collections Manuscripts and Rare Books
The Donald Grady Davidson Papers
multiple
Special Collections Manuscripts and Rare Books
MSS.0002
22.26 linear_feet
Scope and Content Note
The Donald Davidson Papers (1906 - 1968) include correspondence and writings by Davidson as well as reviews, research materials, publications materials, publicity for books, legal and financial documents, family records, newspaper clippings and photographs, segregation materials, and manuscripts of writings by others. The bulk of the materials come from the 1920's through the 1960's.
Davidson received his B. A. and M. A. degrees from Vanderbilt University and remained at the University his entire professional career (1920 - 1968) teaching English. In addition to being a teacher Davidson was also a poet, novelist, and critic. From 1931-1967 he spent his summers teaching at Breadloaf School of English in Ripton, Vermont. He served in the military during World War I May 1917- June 1919. In June of 1918 he married Theresa Sherrer, a legal scholar and artist, and their only child Mary (later Mrs. Eric Bell, Jr.)was born March 26, 1919.
Davidson maintained extensive correspondence with many of his friends and associates who were also important literary figures of this time--John Gould Fletcher, Brainard and Frances Cheney, John Crowe Ransom, Laura Riding, Louis Rubin, Jesse Stuart, Allen Tate, John Donald Wade, Robert Penn Warren, Caroline Gordon/Tate, and Stark Young among others. These letters and others are important highlights of the Davidson Papers and comprise 5 1/3 cubic feet.
The Papers include much information that pertains to Vanderbilt, especially Davidson's role in The Fugitive and Agrarian groups which were centered at the university in the 1920's and 1930's. In the Series Fugitives and Agrarians there are letters and manuscript poems by John Crowe Ransom, Allen Tate, Robert Penn Warren,and other of the Fugitives and Agrarians. Appendix C is a listing of newspaper clippings relating to I'll Take My Stand (1930) and Who Owns America?(1936)
Davidson's Writings (5 1/3 cubic feet) are divided into several genres: poetry, reviews, articles, essays, lectures, text books, history books, plays, a short story and an operetta. His Editing Projects- The Tennessean Book Review and Literary Page and The Weekly Review-A Page About Books cover the period September 7, 1924 - October 26, 1930 and is 1 cubic foot. Of special interest in the Writings is a collection of over 150 of Davidson's poems typed or holograph (Complete listing Appendix A). Davidson's Literary Career is well documented in these papers. Appendix B is a listing of newspaper clippings about Davidson's work. There are also publicity materials and correspondence concerning his various literary projects.
In the Academic Career Series there are Davidson's notes for lectures at Vanderbilt as well as papers by some of his students including Randall Jarrell, Francis Robinson, and Mildred Haun. There are also committee reports and other administrative reports and a small section on Breadloaf School of English. In the Research Notes there are extensive notes for his two volume book The Tennessee and also notes on American Composition and Rhetoric. There are many miscellaneous notes.
Personal and Biographical Materials include Biographical Sketches and Writings about Davidson, Personal and Financial Records and Family Papers. Davidson's own detailed curriculum vita and also that of his wife Theresa Sherrer Davidson are in this series. In the series Organizations, Activities and Events there is 1 1/3 cubic feet of material which is concerned with Segregation and Civil Rights, including Reports of Citizens' Councils in the late 1950's and early 1960's.
The Subject Files contain information on the Tennessee Valley Authority, on George Pullen Jackson, Jesse Stuart, Agriculture, Southern Policy Papers and others. There are also book announcements (arranged by publisher or dealer) and Photographs of Writers (A complete list of these photographs found in Appendix D).
Finally in the Writings By Others there are publications and articles collected by Davidson-- book reviews, poems, and short stories by others, including poems by Cleanth Brooks,, e.e. cummings, Hart Crane,and George Marion O'Donnell.
Donald Davidson Chronology
18 August 1893 Donald Grady Davidson born in Campbellsville, near Pulaski, Tennessee to parents Elma Wells Davidson and Wiliam Bluford Davidson. Both of his parents were teachers-his father a schoolteacher and his mother a piano teacher.
1905 - 1909 Attends and graduates from Branham and Hughes School in Spring Hill, TN.
1909 Begins a B. A. program at Vanderbilt, drops out for financial reasons, returns in 1914.
1910 -1912 Davidson teaches at the Cedar Hill Institute in Cedar Hill, Tennessee.
1912 - 1914 Davidson teaches in the rural community of Mooresville.
Fall 1914 Returns to Vanderbilt at the age of 21.
1915, 1916 Attends George Peabody College for Teachers as a summer student.
1916 - 1917 Teaches in Pulaski, Tennessee where he meets Theresa Sherrer (later to be a legal scholar and artist and Davidson's wife).
1917 Davidson does not graduate with his class in 1916, but receives his B. A. in absentia from Vanderbilt.
May 1917 - June 1919 Davidson serves in the U. S. Military.
May 1917 Davidson joins the first officer candidates who leave Vanderbilt for Fort Oglethorpe in May 1917; commissioned 2nd lieutenant in 324th Infantry, 81st Division, U. S. Army.
August 1917 Lands in Liverpool England.
August 16, 1918 81st Division assembled in Tonnerre France; Davidson sees action in Defensive Sector and Meuse-Argonne offensive; he becomes a first lieutenant.
June 8, 1918 Davidson marries Theresa Sherrer in Greenville, South Carolina while assigned To Camp Sevier.
March 26, 1919 Mary Theresa Davidson born, the only child of Theresa and Donald Davidson (And later Mrs. Eric Bell, Jr.).
June 7, 1919 Leaves to return to America on the USS Martha Washington and arrives in Charleston, South Carolina in mid June.
1919 Davidson begins work on Master's Thesis on Joseph Conrad at Vanderbilt
August 1919 - 1920 Davidson teaches at Kentucky Wesleyan College, Owensboro, Kentucky
Summer 1920 Davidson has a job as a reporter for the Evening Tennesseean
Fall 1920 Davidson begins a 44 year career in the English Department at Vanderbilt University:
1920-1924, Instructor in English
1925-1929, Assistant Professor of English
1930-1937, Associate Professor of English
1938-1964, Professor of English
1964, Distinguished Lecturer in English
1965-1968, Professor of English, Emeritus
1922 M. A. from Vanderbilt (Master's Thesis on Joseph Conrad)
1924 An Outland Piper. Boston: Houghton Mifflin.
1925 Article derived from Davidson's Master's Thesis published in the Spring 1925 issue of the Sewanee Review, "Joseph Conrad's Directed Indirections"
Work on the Master's degree was begun in 1919, and the degree awarded 1922.
April 1922 - Dec.
1925 Fugitive magazine published-Davidson co-founder, 1922 and co-editor, 1922-1924
1926 Poetry Society of South Carolina Southern Prize for "Fire on Belmont Street"
1927 The Tall Men. Boston: Houghton Mifflin
1924 -1930 Sept. 7, 1924 - Oct. 26, 1930 Editor of The Book Review and Literary Page of The Tennessean and The Weekly Review-A Page About Books.
November 1930 I'll Take My Stand: The South and the Agrarian Tradition. By Twelve Southerners. New York: Harper and Brothers. Davidson's essay titled " A Mirror for Artists "
June 1931 Davidson joins the faculty of the Breadloaf School of English of Middlebury College for the summers of 1931 - 1967, Ripton, Vermont.
1934 Culture in the South. Edited by W. T. Couch. Chapel Hill: University of North Carolina Press. Davidson contributes the essay " The Trend of Literature."
Who Owns America? A New Declaration of Independence. Edited by Herbert Agar and Allen Tate. Boston and New York: Houghton Mifflin Co.
1936 Davidson's essay titled " That This Nation May Endure-The Need for Political Regionalism."
1937 British Poetry of the Eighteen Nineties. New York: Doubleday. Davidson is the editor and author of introduction, notes, and biographical sketches.
1938 The Attack on Leviathan: Regionalism and Nationalism in the United States. Chapel Hill: University of North Carolina Press.
1938 Lee in the Mountains and Other Poems. Boston: Houghton Mifflin.
1939 American Composition and Rhetoric (textbook). New York: Scribner.
1942 Readings for Composition (textbook). New York: Scribner. Revised edition, 1957.
1946 The Tennessee Vol. 1, The Old River: Frontier to Secession. New York: Rinehart. Rivers of America Series.
1946 Honorary degree, Litt. D., Cumberland University
1948 Honorary degree, Litt. D., Washington and Lee University
1948 The Tennessee Vol. 2, The New River: Civil War to TVA. New York: Rinehart. Rivers of America Series.
1952 Singin Billy- based on a poem by Davidson, music composed by Charles Faulkner Bryan of George Peabody College for Teachers. Produced at Vanderbilt Theater.
1953 (Author of introduction) Stark Young, So Red the Rose, new edition, Scribner.
1955 Twenty Lessons in Reading and Writing (textbook). New York: Scribner.
1955 - 1959 Davidson Chairman of the Tennessee Federation for Constitutional Government.
May 1956 Fugitive Reunion at Vanderbilt.
1957 Davidson gives the first series of the Eugenia Dorothy Blount Lamar Memorial Lectures at Mercer University in Georgia (Published as Southern Writers in the Modern World).
1957 Still Rebels, Still Yankees and Other Essays. Baton Rouge: Louisiana State University Press.
1958 Southern Writers in the Modern World (Eugenia Lamar Memorial Lectures). Athens: University of Georgia Press.
1961 The Long Street: Poems. Nashville: Vanderbilt University Press.
1963 The Spyglass: Views and Reviews, 1924 - 1930. Edited by John Tyree Fain. Nashville: Vanderbilt University Press.
1964 Davidson retires from Vanderbilt after 44 years.
1965 Honorary degree, L. H. D., Middlebury College.
1966 Poems, 1922 - 1961. Minneapolis: University of Minnesota Press.
1966 ( Editor and author of introduction) John Donald Wade, Selected Essays and Other Writings. Athens: University of Georgia Press.
Spring 1968 Reunion of the Agrarians at the University of Dallas; Davidson unable to attend because of failing health.
April 25, 1968 Donald Davidson dies in his home at the age of 74. Funeral service April 27, 1968 in Nashville.
1974 The Literary Correspondence of Donald Davidson and Allen Tate. Edited by John Tyree Fain and Thomas Daniel Young. Athens: University of Georgia Press.
1985 Singin Billy: A Folk Opera. Text by Donald Davidson; music by Charles Faulkner Bryan. Glendale, S. C.: Foundation for American Education.
1996 The Big Ballad Jamboree. Jackson: University Press of Mississippi.
- General Correspondence
  - Correspondence--Outgoing
    - April 1, 1906 - October 26, 1918 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - October 31, 1918 - February 16, 1919 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - February 22, 1919 - May 4, 1919 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - May 12, 1919 - August 13, 1922 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - August 23, 1022 - November 8, 1922 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - December 2, 1922 - March 10, 1923 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - March 19, 1923 - June 28, 1923 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - August 14, 1923 - November25, 1923 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - December 3, 1923 - March 21, 1926 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - August 17, 1926 - April 9, 1927 (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - May 29, 1927 - October 2, 1927 (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - February 13, 1928 - January 14, 1929 (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - January 17, 1929 - December 18, 1929 (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - January 1, 1930 - March 17, 1930 (Box 1, Folder 14)
    - March 17, 1930 - May 3, 1930 (Box 1, Folder 15)
    - June 14, 1930 - September 20, 1930 (Box 1, Folder 16)
    - September 27, 1930 - November 26, 1930 (Box 1, Folder 17)
    - December 1, 1930 - February 28, 1931 (Box 1, Folder 18)
    - March 8, 1931 - October 11, 1931 (Box 1, Folder 19)
    - March 29, 1932 - May 2, 1932 (Box 1, Folder 20)
    - May 15, 1932 - December 11, 1932 (Box 1, Folder 21)
    - March 13, 1933 - April 7, 1933 (Box 1, Folder 22)
    - April 16, 1933 - December 17, 1933 (Box 1, Folder 23)
    - January 5, 1934 - February 20, 1934 (Box 1, Folder 24)
    - March 3, 1934 - March 5, 1934 (Box 1, Folder 25)
    - March 13, 1934 - December 11, 1934 (Box 1, Folder 26)
    - January 9, 1935 - March 6, 1935 (Box 1, Folder 27)
    - March 12, 1935 - March 17, 1935 (Box 1, Folder 28)
    - March 19, 1935 - April 20, 1935 (Box 1, Folder 29)
    - April 21, 1935 - May 21, 1935 (Box 1, Folder 30)
    - March 28, 1935 - June 15, 1935 (Box 1, Folder 31)
    - June 25, 1935 - October 14, 1935 (Box 1, Folder 32)
    - October 16, 1935 - February 6, 1936 (Box 1, Folder 33)
    - March 25, 1936 - April 29, 1936 (Box 1, Folder 34)
    - May 24, 1936 - June 15, 1936 (Box 1, Folder 35)
    - June 18, 1936 - February 27, 1937 (Box 1, Folder 36)
    - March 5, 1937 - May 12, 1937 (Box 1, Folder 37)
    - June 1, 1937 - January 7, 1938 (Box 1, Folder 38)
    - March 11, 1938 - April 26, 1938 (Box 1, Folder 39)
    - April 28, 1938 - May 16, 1938 (Box 1, Folder 40)
    - May 20, 1938 - June 19, 1938 (Box 1, Folder 41)
    - June 19, 1938 - October 4, 1938 (Box 1, Folder 42)
    - October 15, 1938 - October 22, 1938 (Box 1, Folder 43)
    - November 6, 1938 - December 6, 1938 (Box 1, Folder 44)
    - December 14, 1938 - December 31, 1938 (Box 1, Folder 45)
    - January 1, 1939 - April 19, 1939 (Box 1, Folder 46)
    - April 30, 1939 (Box 1, Folder 47)
    - May 9, 1939 - December 3, 1939 (Box 1, Folder 48)
    - January 14, 1940 - May 19, 1940 (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - June 2, 1940 - July 22, 1940 (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - August 6, 1940 (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - August 26, 1940 - April 20, 1941 (Box 2, Folder 4)
    - May 22, 1941 - November 26, 1941 (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - January 8, 1942 - December 12, 1942 (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - January 31,1943 - March 5, 1943 (Box 2, Folder 7)
    - March 6, 1943 - September 4,1943 (Box 2, Folder 8)
    - November 6, 1943 - November 2, 1944 (Box 2, Folder 9)
    - November 7, 1944 - March 24, 1945 (Box 2, Folder 10)
    - March 31, 1945 - April 2, 1945 (Box 2, Folder 11)
    - April 3, 1945 - October 17, 1945 (Box 2, Folder 12)
    - October 29, 1945 - February 14, 1946 (Box 2, Folder 13)
    - March 7, 1946 - April 2, 1946 (Box 2, Folder 14)
    - April 5, 1946 - July 12, 1946 (Box 2, Folder 15)
    - August 18, 1946 - December 6, 1946 (Box 2, Folder 16)
    - January 7, 1947 - March 23, 1947 (Box 2, Folder 17)
    - March 24, 1947- June 15, 1947 (Box 2, Folder 18)
    - July 1, 1947 - August 10, 1947 (Box 2, Folder 19)
    - September 9, 1947 - October 30, 1947 (Box 2, Folder 20)
    - December 13, 1947 - January 31, 1948 (Box 2, Folder 21)
    - March 3, 1948 - December 1, 1948 (Box 2, Folder 22)
    - December 10, 1948 - January 2, 1949 (Box 2, Folder 23)
    - January 18, 1949 - March 25, 1949 (Box 2, Folder 24)
    - April 27, 1949 - June 21, 1949 (Box 2, Folder 25)
    - July 11, 1949 - October 19, 1949 (Box 2, Folder 26)
    - October 31, 1949 - December 8, 1949 (Box 2, Folder 27)
    - January 9, 1950 - February 26, 1950 (Box 2, Folder 28)
    - March 5, 1950 - April 30, 1950 (Box 2, Folder 29)
    - May 9, 1950 - May 30, 1950 (Box 2, Folder 30)
    - June 7, 1950 - January 31,1951 (Box 2, Folder 31)
    - February 8, 1951 - August 15, 1951 (Box 2, Folder 32)
    - August 4, 1951 - March 12, 1952 (Box 2, Folder 33)
    - March 26, 1952 - May 28, 1952 (Box 2, Folder 34)
    - August 4, 1952 - January 14, 1953 (Box 2, Folder 35)
    - January 21, 1953 - June 15, 1953 (Box 2, Folder 36)
    - August 10, 1953 - September 10, 1953 (Box 2, Folder 37)
    - September 17, 1953 - October 24, 1953 (Box 2, Folder 38)
    - October 28, 1953 - December 15, 1953 (Box 3, Folder 1)
    - December 16, 1953 - January 13, 1954 (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - January 18, 1954 - February 23, 1954 (Box 3, Folder 3)
    - February 24, 1954 - March 17, 1954 (Box 3, Folder 4)
    - March 21, 1954 - April 15, 1954 (Box 3, Folder 5)
    - April 22, 1954 - May 28, 1954 (Box 3, Folder 6)
    - May 29, 1954 - August 17, 1954 (Box 3, Folder 7)
    - August 31, 1954 - December 5,1954 (Box 3, Folder 8)
    - December 10, 1954 - February 18, 1955 (Box 3, Folder 9)
    - February 22, 1955 - May 6, 1955 (Box 3, Folder 10)
    - May 8, 1955 - July 2, 1955 (Box 3, Folder 11)
    - July 13, 1955 - September 25, 1955 (Box 3, Folder 12)
    - September 30, 1955 - May 16, 1956 (Box 3, Folder 13)
    - May 26, 1954 - July 25, 1956 (Box 3, Folder 14)
    - July 30, 1956 - September 2, 1956 (Box 3, Folder 15)
    - September 14, 1956 - October 15 1956 (Box 3, Folder 16)
    - October 16,1956 - April 14, 1957 (Box 3, Folder 17)
    - July 21, 1957 - June 29, 1958 (Box 3, Folder 18)
    - July 18, 1958 - October 13, 1959 (Box 3, Folder 19)
    - November 3, 1959 - February 21, 1960 (Box 3, Folder 20)
    - February 24, 1960 - August 19, 1960 (Box 3, Folder 21)
    - August 21, 1960 - October 26, 1960 (Box 3, Folder 22)
    - November 13, 1960 - February 21, 1961 (Box 3, Folder 23)
    - February 23, 1961 - October 23, 1961 (Box 3, Folder 24)
    - November 5, 1961 - December 19, 1961 (Box 3, Folder 25)
    - February 8, 1962 - July 16, 1962 (Box 3, Folder 26)
    - July 21, 1962 - January 31, 1963 (Box 3, Folder 27)
    - February 1, 1963 - September 5, 1963 (Box 3, Folder 28)
    - October 16, 1963 - February 26, 1964 (Box 3, Folder 29)
    - March 14, 1964 - December 19, 1964 (Box 3, Folder 30)
    - January 24, 1965 - May 2, 1966 (Box 3, Folder 31)
    - May 28, 1966 - August 7, 1966 (Box 3, Folder 32)
    - August 15, 1966 - March 14, 1967 (Box 3, Folder 33)
    - April 2, 1967 - November 3, 1967 (Box 3, Folder 34)
    - January 14, 1968 - April 5, 1968 (Box 3, Folder 35)
    - Undated No. 1 (Box 3, Folder 36)
    - Undated No. 2 (Box 3, Folder 37)
    - Undated No. 3 (Box 3, Folder 38)
    - Fragments and Rough Drafts of Telegrams (Box 3, Folder 39)
  - Correspondence --Incoming
    - A - Aborn (Box 4, Folder 1)
    - Acklen - Adams, Mary E. (Box 4, Folder 2)
    - Aden - Agar (Box 4, Folder 3)
    - Ahearn - Alexander, Harvey (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - Alexander, T. H. (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - Alexander, Tom - Allen, Charles (Box 4, Folder 6)
    - Allen, Hervey No. 1 (Box 4, Folder 7)
    - Allen, Hervey No. 2 (Box 4, Folder 8)
    - Allen, Hervey No. 3 (Box 4, Folder 9)
    - Allen, Jane - Allen, Ward (Box 4, Folder 10)
    - Alliance of Agrarian and Distributist Groups, Comm. For the- Andrews and Almon (Box 4, Folder 11)
    - Ames - Archibald (Box 4, Folder 12)
    - Armstrong, Walter P. (Box 4, Folder 13)
    - Armstrong, Zella - Aymard (Box 4, Folder 14)
    - Babcock - Bailey (Box 4, Folder 15)
    - Baker - Ball, Faith No. 1 (Box 4, Folder 16)
    - Ball, Faith (No. 2) - Barder (Box 4, Folder 17)
    - Barker - Barnwell, C. H. (Box 4, Folder 18)
    - Barr - Barrow (Box 4, Folder 19)
    - Bartlett - Battey (Box 4, Folder 20)
    - Battle - Beach (Box 4, Folder 21)
    - Beaird - Beatty, [1937] (Box 4, Folder 22)
    - Beatty [1940] - Beck (Box 4, Folder 23)
    - Bell (Box 4, Folder 24)
    - Benet - Berlin (Box 4, Folder 25)
    - Best - Bjorkman (Box 4, Folder 26)
    - Black - Blankenship (Box 4, Folder 27)
    - Bledsoe - Boland (Box 4, Folder 28)
    - Bond, R. P. (Box 4, Folder 29)
    - Bond - Borsodi (Box 4, Folder 30)
    - Bostell - Bosworth (Box 4, Folder 31)
    - Bowers - Bowling (Box 4, Folder 32)
    - Boyd - Brandon (Box 4, Folder 33)
    - Branscomb, Harvie (Box 4, Folder 34)
    - Breadloaf School of English (Box 4, Folder 35)
    - Breast - Breyer (Box 4, Folder 36)
    - Brickell- Bromley (Box 4, Folder 37)
    - Brooks, Cleanth, Jr. (No. 1) (Box 4, Folder 38)
    - Brooks, Cleanth, Jr. (No. 2) - Brooks, Paul (Box 4, Folder 39)
    - Broome - Brown, Maud Marion (Box 4, Folder 40)
    - Brown, O. E. - Brown, W.L. (No. 1) (Box 4, Folder 41)
    - Brown, Wm L. [No. 2] - Buchanan (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - Buck - Butler (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - Bynner, Witter [ No. 1] (Box 5, Folder 3)
    - Bynner, Witter [ No. 2 ] - Byrnes (Box 5, Folder 4)
    - Cabeen - Campbell, Harry, [1953] (Box 5, Folder 5)
    - Campbell, Harry, [1954] (Box 5, Folder 6)
    - Campbell, Harry [ 1960] - Campbell, Robert C. (Box 5, Folder 7)
    - Campbell, Ruth E. - Campbell, W. B., [ 1928] (Box 5, Folder 8)
    - Campbell, W. B., [1929] (Box 5, Folder 9)
    - Campbell, W. B., [April 1930] (Box 5, Folder 10)
    - Campbell, W. B. [May 1930] - Canby (Box 5, Folder 11)
    - Capeci - Carmichael, Peter A. (Box 5, Folder 12)
    - Carroll - Cason (Box 5, Folder 13)
    - Caswell, A.Remington, [ 1930 - Feb. 1931] (Box 5, Folder 14)
    - Caswell, A. Remington, [ March - May 1931] (Box 5, Folder 15)
    - Chadsey, C. P. - Chambers (Box 5, Folder 16)
    - Chambliss - Chapman, A. (Box 5, Folder 17)
    - Chapman, M. - Chase, R. (1) (Box 5, Folder 18)
    - Chase, R. (2) - Cheney, Lon (1946) (Box 5, Folder 19)
    - Cheney, Lon [1948] - Chodoron (Box 5, Folder 20)
    - Ciardi - Clarke (Box 5, Folder 21)
    - Cleaton (Box 5, Folder 22)
    - Clemens - Colby (Box 5, Folder 23)
    - Cole - Collins, A. C. (Box 5, Folder 24)
    - Collins, S., [1931 -37] (Box 5, Folder 25)
    - Collins [1948 - N. D.] - Conry (Box 5, Folder 26)
    - Constiner - Cornell (Box 5, Folder 27)
    - Corps. HQS. - Couch, [ May 6, 1932] (Box 5, Folder 28)
    - Couch, [May 21, 1932 -1934] (Box 5, Folder 29)
    - Couch, [1937 - 1943] (Box 5, Folder 30)
    - Couch, 1948-1955, N.D. (Box 5, Folder 31)
    - Cousins, R. B. (Box 5, Folder 32)
    - Cowan, Louise (Box 5, Folder 33)
    - Cowan, Louise (Box 5, Folder 34)
    - Cow - Crabb (Box 5, Folder 35)
    - Craig - Crawford, [1946] (Box 5, Folder 36)
    - Crawford, [1947 - 53] (Box 5, Folder 37)
    - Creighton - Cugnot (Box 5, Folder 38)
    - Cullon - Curry, W. C., [ 1923] (Box 5, Folder 39)
    - Curry, W. C. [1924 -62] - Cutting (Box 5, Folder 40)
    - Dabbs - Dargan, [May, 1924] (Box 6, Folder 1)
    - Dargan - Davidson, John W. (Box 6, Folder 2)
    - Davidson, Levette J. - Davidson, Thomas (Box 6, Folder 3)
    - Davidson, Thomas - Davidson, William (Box 6, Folder 4)
    - Davies - Davis, Lambert, [1930] (Box 6, Folder 5)
    - Davis, Lambert, [1934-35] (Box 6, Folder 6)
    - Davis, Lambert, [1939 -48] (Box 6, Folder 7)
    - Davis, Lambert [1949] - Davis, Lillian Perrine (Box 6, Folder 8)
    - Dawson - De Bellis (Box 6, Folder 9)
    - Deeds - Doane (Box 6, Folder 10)
    - Dodd, Richard E. and Clare (Box 6, Folder 11)
    - Dodd, Richard E. (Box 6, Folder 12)
    - Dodd, Richard E. and Clare (Box 6, Folder 13)
    - Dodd, Richard E. and Clare (Box 6, Folder 14)
    - Dodson - Dorrance, [1938] (Box 6, Folder 15)
    - Dodson - Dorrance, [1938] (Box 6, Folder 16)
    - Dorrance [1939] - Dos Passos (Box 6, Folder 17)
    - Douglas - Drake (Box 6, Folder 18)
    - Draper - Dresbach (Box 6, Folder 19)
    - Drew - Durr (Box 6, Folder 20)
    - Dutton - Dye (Box 6, Folder 21)
    - Eagel - Edmunds (Box 6, Folder 22)
    - Edwards - Eisenby (Box 6, Folder 23)
    - Ellegood (Box 6, Folder 24)
    - Elliott, E. H. - Elliott, W. Y., [1958] (Box 6, Folder 25)
    - Elliott, W. Y. [1960] - Ellis (Box 6, Folder 26)
    - Ellison - Engle (Box 6, Folder 27)
    - Epperson - Everitt (Box 6, Folder 28)
    - Faber - Farrar, [ 1940] (Box 6, Folder 29)
    - Farrar [1941] - Faulkner (Box 6, Folder 30)
    - Fauntleroy - Ferree (Box 6, Folder 31)
    - Ferris - Finney (Box 6, Folder 32)
    - Fishwick - Flanders, [1950] (Box 6, Folder 33)
    - Flanders - Fletcher, Charlie May (Box 6, Folder 34)
    - Fletcher, J. G., [March 25,1927 - Feb. 4, 1931] (Box 6, Folder 35)
    - Fletcher, J. G., [April, 1933 - March 1934] (Box 7, Folder 1)
    - Fletcher, J. G., [Oct. 1934 - March 5, 1935] (Box 7, Folder 2)